

Nationality: Argentinean

Email: romina.villaverde@gmail.com
Website: www.romivillaverde.com
Phone: +54 911 6609 5667
LinkedIn: @rominavillaverde
GitHub: @rvillaverde

SKILLS

DESIGN

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Illustrator

FRONT-END

HTML5

CSS3

Less - Sass

JavaScript

Jquery

Material IO

AngularJS

React

BACK-END

NodeJS

Ruby on Rails

Java

Relational databases

APIs

SPOKEN LANGUAGES

Spanish

English

Portuguese

INTERESTS

- Photography
- Music
- Cycling

ROMINA VILLAVERDE BACSKAY FULL STACK DEVELOPER

PROFILE

Full stack developer with over 10 years experience working with different companies and technologies. Proactive and deeply analytical, as well as creative, curious and detail-oriented. I have a great autodidact ability, as I'm always looking to learn new things to improve my work. Currently working freelance for different clients, designing and developing websites and applications.

EXPERIENCE

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Freelance Mar 2016 - present

- Active freelance web designer and developer.
 - Website development with CMS support.
 - E-commerce shop development.

PROGRAMMING MENTOR

Acamica Aug 2016 - Dec 2016 Mentor for "Aprendé Programando", a four-month course which goal is to teach teenagers who don't have any knowledge about programming how to develop websites.

JAVA DEVELOPER

SCV Soft Sep 2014 - Sep 2015 REST API developer.

Technologies used: Java, MySQL, ElasticSearch, REST Apis.

RUBY ON RAILS DEVELOPER

SCV Soft Jun 2013 - Aug 2014 Ruby on Rails web application developer for an important comprany from the USA.

Technologies used: Ruby on Rails, Javascript, Jquery, HTML5, CSS3, Sass, AngularJS, MySQL, RSpec.

RUBY ON RAILS DEVELOPER

Three Pillar Global Aug 2012 - Mar 2013 Web development in Ruby on Rails for a US based client.
 Technologies used: Ruby on Rails, JavaScript, JQuery, Ajax,
 HTML, HAML, Sass, PostgreSQL.

MOBILE DEVELOPER

Three Pillar Global Aug 2011 - Aug 2012 Android and Blackberry developer.

Technologies used: Java, Android SDK, BlackBerry JDE, MySQL, JavaScript, Ajax, JSP, HTML, Apache Tomcat, Maven, Ant.

GAME DEVELOPER

Metrogames Apr 2010 - Aug 2011 Game developer for Facebook platform.

Technologies used: ActionScript, Flash, FlexBuilder.

JAVA DEVELOPER

Dinmax Consulting Nov 2008 - Apr 2010 Application developer for several companies in Argentina.
 Technologies used: Java, GWT, Hibernate, servlets, Jasper Report, PostgreSQL, XML, JSon, JUnit, Eolipse.

CUSTOMER CARE REPRESENTATIVE

TeleTech Nov 2006 - Mar 2008 Billingual customer care representative for a US based company.

EDUCATION

UNIVERSIDAD DE BUENOS AIRES

Computer Science 2006 - 2010 (Unfinished)